Dunne, John R.; Papers apap244
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
John R. Dunne Papers
1943-1970
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap244
16.2 cubic ft.
This collection documents John R. Dunne's first years of service in the New York State Senate, from the mid-1960s until 1970.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
John R. Dunne initially donated his papers to Syracuse University in a series of acquisitions in 1969-1970. The papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2006.
Biographical History
John R. Dunne was born in Baldwin, New York on January 28, 1930. Dunne graduated from Georgetown University in 1951 and attended Yale Law School soon after. He served as a Republican member of the New York State Senate from Long Island from 1966 until retiring in 1989 to practice law.
During his time in the Senate, Dunne served as Deputy Majority Leader, Chair of the Judiciary Committee, Chair of the Insurance Committee, and Chair of the Joint Legislative Committee on Crime and Corrections. While in office, Dunne advocated for progressive social issues while working alongside other state senators to get laws and bills passed. These laws and bills can be found in Dunne's collection.
Dunne is most famously known for his involvement in the Attica prison protest in 1971 as chief negotiator and later helped to found the Prisoners' Legal Services of New York.
From 1990-1993, Dunne served as Assistant Attorney General for Civil Rights under President George H.W. Bush. He was senior counsel to the Albany-based Whiteman Osterman & Hanna law firm at the time of his death.
Dunne died on November 1, 2020 and was survived by his wife of 62 years, Denise Maher Dunne, their four children, and nine grandchildren.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains papers from John Dunne's career as New York State Senator. While Dunne is primarily known for his work during the Attica prison protest in 1971, Dunne's collection does not provide any further details on his involvement. Instead, the Dunne Papers contain Dunne's earlier legislative work including Senate bills to interactions with constituents to correspondence. The legislation that Dunne sponsored ranges from abortion related bills to funding for education in Long Island school districts to corrections law.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged into two series - Subject Files and Legislation. Subject Files is arranged alphabetically and Legislation is arranged by bill number.
Politics and Politicians; Politicians--New York (State); Dunne, John R.
- Subject Files, 1943-1970; 1; 11.4 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  In this series, the topics range from abortion and education to transportation and medical treatments. The abortion files display the different opinions of senators along with Dunne's personal beliefs pertaining to the issue. The education files discuss different practices and initiatives to advance Long Island schools and school districts. The medical files discuss the requirements to receive different medical assistance programs such as Medicaid.
  There is also a significant amount of correspondence contained in the series. These include requests to and from constituents to debriefs pertaining to different meetings. Researchers who are interested in both Dunne's personal and professional contacts would find correspondence files in this collection especially useful.
  - A, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAA, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abortion, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abortion, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abortion, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Abortion Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Abortion Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adult Education, 1968; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Aging, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Agreeance Form Letters, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Agreeance Form Letters (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Agreeance Form Letters (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Agriculture, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AI 828, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Aid to Education, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Air Pollution, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Air Pollution, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Air Pollution Bill, 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alcoholism, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Amended Penal Code, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Animals, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Animals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Anti-Discrimination for [Individuals with Intellectual Disabilities], 1958; 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anti-Riot Legislation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arts, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Assembly Notices, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Aurora-Air Pollution Device, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - B, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - B, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - B, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bake Stamped Bread, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Baking (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Baking (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Banking, 1966; 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Banking District Lines/Branches/Interest, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Better Business Bureau, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bill Board, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Biography, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Blaine Amendment, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Blank Questionnaire, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Board of Education District No.22, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - BOCES, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bridge (1 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bridge (2 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Budget-State, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Budget Request for Mentally Ill, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Business, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Business Development CORP, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bussing (1 of 3), 1963; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bussing (2 of 3), 1963; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bussing (3 of 3), 1963; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bussing, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - C, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - C, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - C, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campaign, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Calling Cards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Children, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chiropractic, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey INC., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Citizens Union, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - City University, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Civil Service, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Civil Service and Pensions Committee, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Civil Service Employee Association, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Civil Service Employee Raise, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Civilian Review Boards, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Clubs and Organizations, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Codes Committee, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Commissioners of Improvement Districts, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Committee Notices, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Committee Reports, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Committee Reports and Business, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Committee Sheets, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Committee Men for 6th Sen. District, 1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Commuter Tax (1 of 2), 1943; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Commuter Tax (2 of 2), 1943; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Compulsory Health Insurance, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Concurrent Resolution, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Condolences, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Condon-Wadlin, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Condon-Wadlin, 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Congratulatory, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Congratulatory, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Conservation, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Conservation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Conservative Party, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Conservative Party, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Consumer Prices, 1965; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Constituent Mail, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Constitution-New York State, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Contract Laboratories, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correction, 1964; 1966-1967; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correction, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correction For Penal Institution Committee (1 of 2), 1960; 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correction For Penal Institution Committee (2 of 2), 1960; 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to be Filled, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "A", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "B", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "C", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "D", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "F", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "G", 1967-1968; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "H", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "K", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "L", 1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "M" (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "M" (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "R", 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "S", 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "T", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with Last Name "W", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Criminal Law, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Criminal Procedure Law, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Credit Agreements, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Credit Cards, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Criminal Convictions for Motorist, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - D, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - D, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - D, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Debate Letters, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Decentralization, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Decentralization Correspondence, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Declinations, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Declinations, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dental Identity, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dental Society, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dentist Form Letter, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Department of Transportation, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Divorce, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Divorce-In Support Of, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Domestic Relations: Divorce, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Draft Acts Relating to Penal Law and Criminal Procedure, 1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - E, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - E, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - E, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Economic Opportunity, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Education (1 of 2), 1965-1967; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Education (2 of 2), 1965-1967; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Education, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Includes the Campus Plan for State University of New York.
  - Education, Dominick-Kottler Bill (1 of 2), 1967; Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Education, Dominick-Kottler Bill (2 of 2), 1967; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Education, Committee (1 of 2), 1965-1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Education, Committee (2 of 2), 1965-1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Education Committee, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Education for Mentally Ill, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Edward M. Edel, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Election Returns, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Elmont Clean-Up, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Elmont Youth Project, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Ethics, 1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - F, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - F, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Federal-State Aid, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fiduciary Commission Bill, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Firearms, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Firearms, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Firearms, 1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fiscal (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Flags, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ford Instrument Company, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Form Letters From Dunne, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fortune Society, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Friends of Mercy Hospital-Committee, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Funeral Directors Cost-Opposed, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Future, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - G, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - G, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - G, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Garbage, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Gambling, 1966; Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Garden City, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Garden City Nursery, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - General Reply (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - General Reply (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Government Spending, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Governor's Messages, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Governor's Press Releases, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Gun Rights/Ownership, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Guns, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - H, 1966; Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - H, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - H, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Head Start, 1965; Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Health, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Health, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Health, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Hoffman Ski Development, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Holding Tank Form, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Holiday Closing Form Letter, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Home Solicitation Sales, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Housing, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Housing, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Humane Slaughter, 1963; 1965-1968; Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Humor-Political, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - I, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - I, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - I, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Ideas, 1964; 1966 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Industry Accidents, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Insurance, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Insurance, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Interior Designs Licensing, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Invitations, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Invitations, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - J, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - J, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - J, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Jet Noise, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Journal Clerk Sheets, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Cerebral Palsy (1 of 2), 1950; 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Cerebral Palsy (2 of 2), 1950; 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Judicial Selection, 1967; Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Journal Clerk Sheets, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Journal Clerk Signatures, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Judgeships, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Judicial Reform, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - K, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - K, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - K, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - L, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - L, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - L, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Labor, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Labor and Industry Committee, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Law Day, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Law Revision Commission, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - League of Women Voters, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - League of Women Voters, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Legal Assistance Corporation, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Legislation Affecting Teachers, 1967; Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Index Forms, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Reform, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Research, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Legislature, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Letters of Thanks to People in Nebraska and Missouri Following Trip, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Letters with Wardens, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Liberal Party, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lie Detector, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lists, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - LJE, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Lobbyists (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lobbyists (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lobbyists, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Long Island Better Business Bureau, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Long Island Railroad, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Long Island Railroad, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Long Island Railroad Strike, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Lottery, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Lowering Voting Age, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Loyalty Oath and Elimination, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - M, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - M, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - M, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Mailing Lists (1 of 2), 1965-1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mailing Lists (2 of 2), 1965-1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mailings, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Malverne School Controversy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - March Hearings, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Maps, 1965; Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mayor's Budget (1 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mayor's Budget (2 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - MC, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - MC, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - McGinnis, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Meat Bill, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Medicaid, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Medicaid, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Medicaid, Background and Research (1 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Medicaid, Background and Research (2 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Medicaid, Correspondence, 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Medicaid, Legislation (1 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Medicaid, Legislation (2 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Medicaid Newspaper Clippings, 1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Medical, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Memo From New York State Senate, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Memos From Finance Community, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - [Mental Health], 1966-1967; Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Mental Hygiene, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Metcalf-Hatch Act Correspondence, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Commuter Transportation, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Opera, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Military Training Correspondence, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Missouri Plan, 1945; 1965-1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Mortgage Interest Rates, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Motor Vehicles (1 of 2), 1963-1966; Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Motor Vehicles (2 of 2), 1963-1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Municipal, 1964-1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Municipal, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Museum and Program, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - N, 1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - N, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - N, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Narcotics, 1956; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Nassau County (1 of 3), 1964-1967; Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nassau County (2 of 3), 1964-1967; Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Nassau County (3 of 3), 1964-1967; Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Nassau County District Court, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Nassau County Legal Services Program, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Nassau County Water Authority, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Nassau County Water Authority, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Nassau County Water Authority, 1969; Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - National Federation of Independent Business-Ballots, 1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Neighborhood Schools, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - New York City, 1964; 1966 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - New York City Fiscal, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - New York State Red Book, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - News Release, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Newsday, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Newsletter, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Lists, 1967; Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Newspapers, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - No Reply (1 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - No Reply (2 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Non-Committal, 1966; Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Non-Committal, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Non-Committal, 1968; Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Non-Committal, 1969; Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Non-Profit Institutions, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Notices, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Nurses, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Nurses' Training, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Nursing Homes, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - O, 1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - O, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - O, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ombudsman, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ombudsman Correspondent, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Open Parks, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Out-of-State Scholarships, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Over 65, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - P, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - P, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - P, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlets, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Patronage, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Patronage, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Penal Institution, 1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Penal Institution Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Penal Institution-Research, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Pensions, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Personal, 1965-1967; Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Physical Therapists, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Plan Selection of Missouri Judge, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Photographs Taken December 17, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Places to visit, 1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Podiatrists, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Police (1 of 2), 1965-1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Police (2 of 2), 1965-1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Pollution, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Polytechnic Institute, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Population Data, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Pornographic Material, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Poverty Programs, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Private Clubs, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Probation and Parole, 1968; Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Profile of Sixth, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Programs, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Psychologists Correspondence, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Publications, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Public Works, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Public Works, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Q, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Q, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Quarter Horse Racing Correspondence, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - R, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - R, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - R, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Racing, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Railroad, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Reapportionment, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Reapportionment - Local Government, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Recidivism Projects, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Recreation, Undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Red Books, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Red Book and Manual List, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Red Book and Manual Lists, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Regents Recommendations, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Regents Scholarship, 1966; Undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Regents Scholarship, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Released Press Releases (1 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Released Press Releases (2 of 2), 1966; Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Religion, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Religious, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Rent Control, 1969; Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)